Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Gubernatorial Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1941-1976 (Boxes 128-554, 772-773, Film shelf)
  - Economic situation, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 367: 1)
    Includes conference material.
  - Multi-state tax compact, 1974 (Box-folder 367: 2)
  - Agriculture and Services Agency, Commerce
    - Lockheed, 1971 (Box-folder 367: 3)
    - Motion picture industry, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 367: 4)
    - Task Force on Aerospace-Aviation Education, 1973 (Box-folder 367: 5)
  - Labor-Management Task Force on Construction Industry, 1970 (Box-folder 367: 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1968 (Box-folder 367: 7)
  - Hunter's Point, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 367: 8)
  - Task Force on Evaluation of Win, undated (Box-folder 367: 9)
  - Agriculture and Services Agency, Commerce, U.S.-California economy, inflation-recession, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 367: 10)
  - Inflation control, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 367: 11-12)
  - Wage and price control, 1971 (Box-folder 367: 13)
  - Economic Stabilization Program, Phase IV Health Care Costs, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 367: 14)
  - Market Outlook, published by PG&E, 1973 (Box-folder 367: 15)
  - San Francisco Bay Area Report: A Study of Growth and Economic Stature, published by Security Pacific National Bank, 1971 (Box-folder 367: 16)
  - The Southern California Report: A Study of Growth and Economic Stature, published by Security Pacific National Bank, 1970 (Box-folder 368: 1)
  - Perspectives for the '70s and '80s: Tomorrow's Problems Confronting Today's Management, 1970 (Box-folder 368: 2)
  - California: People, Problems, Potential, published by Bank of America, 1970 (Box-folder 368: 3)
  - Pacific Business, published by the California Chamber of Commerce, 1972 May/June (Box-folder 368: 4)
  - "Economic Stabilization Report," Office of Emergency Services, 1971 September 7 (Box-folder 368: 5)
  - President's wage and price freeze, 1971 (Box-folder 369: 1-4)
  - President's order on wages and salaries, 1971 (Box-folder 369: 5)
  - Business and Transportation Agency
    - Documents, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 370: 1-8)
    - Documents (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 371: 1-7)
    - Agency, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 371: 8)
    - Agency, undated (Box-folder 372: 1)
    - Miscellany, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 372: 2-7)
    - Miscellany (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 373: 1-2)
    - Symposium on Business Regulation, 1973 April 27 (Box-folder 373: 3)
    - Business and transportation legislation, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 373: 4-8)
    - Department of Real Estate Office of Interstate Land Sales Registration, 1974 (Box-folder 373: 9)
    - Office of Interstate Land Sales Registration, 1974 (Box-folder 373: 10)
    - California Highway Patrol special projects, 1968, 1970 (Box-folder 373: 11)
    - Federal Bill No. H.R. 11597, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 373: 12)
    - Department of California Highway Patrol, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 373: 13)
    - Traffic, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 373: 14)
    - Directors report, California Association of Highway Patrolmen, 1971 May (Box-folder 374: 1)
    - Governor's Automobile Accident Study Commission: Volumes I-III, 1970 (Box-folder 374: 2-3)
    - Report of fatal and injury motor vehicle traffic accidents, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 374: 4)
    - Reports on motorcycle accidents and operation 500, 1970 (Box-folder 374: 5)
    - Operation 101, 1972 April (Box-folder 374: 6)
    - Jacobs study, plan for a career development program, 1972 (Box-folder 374: 7)
    - "Doing Business in California" reports, 1973 (Box-folder 374: 8)
    - Department of Corporations, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 375: 1-2)
    - Department of Savings and Loan, 1971, 1973 (Box-folder 375: 3)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1969, 1974 (Box-folder 375: 4)
    - "A Review of DMV On-Line Issuance Policy,", 1972 (Box-folder 375: 5)
    - Task Force on Credit and Personnel Reporting Practices, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 375: 6)
    - Usury, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 375: 7)
    - Alcoholic beverage fair trade, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 375: 8)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 375: 9)
    - Urban affairs, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 375: 10)
    - Urban development, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 375: 11)
    - Title VIII of the Federal Housing Act of 1964, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 375: 12)
    - "The States and the Urban Crisis,", 1970 (Box-folder 375: 13)
    - Annual reports by the Department of Housing and Community Development, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 375: 14)
    - "Toward Urban Progress" report, 1970 (Box-folder 375: 15)
    - Various reports on urban America, 1967, 1970 (Box-folder 375: 16)
    - "Financing the Nation's Housing Needs,", 1973 (Box-folder 375: 17)
    - "A Report on the Feasibility and Desirability of State Involvement in Housing Finance in California,", 1974 (Box-folder 376: 1)
    - "Why the Wheels: The Immobile Home," report published by the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 376: 2)
    - City: Magazine of Urban Life and Environment, 1970 August-September (Box-folder 376: 3)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 376: 4)
    - California Housing Finance Corporation, 1974 (Box-folder 376: 5)
    - Community development series, 1968 (Box-folder 376: 6)
    - Model Cities Program, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 376: 7-8)
    - California's application for funds under Title VIII of the Housing Act of 1964 (Box-folder 376: 9)
    - California model cities and revenue sharing, 1972 (Box-folder 376: 10)
    - Oakland City Center Project, 1972 (Box-folder 376: 11)
    - No fault automobile insurance legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 377: 1)
    - No Fault Task Force, 1972 (Box-folder 377: 2)
    - Auto insurance legislation, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 377: 3)
    - No fault insurance, 1972 (Box-folder 377: 4)
    - Illinois Department of Insurance, 1971 (Box-folder 377: 5)
    - No fault insurance information from conference in Puerto Rico, 1971 (Box-folder 377: 6-7)
    - Aviation, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 377: 8)
    - Task Force on Transportation, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 377: 9)
    - Mass transit, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 377: 10)
    - BART (Bay Area Rapid Transit), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 377: 11)
    - Task Force for Development of Antelope Valley, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 377: 12)
    - "Annual Report," published by Southern California Rapid Transit District, 1970 (Box-folder 378: 1)
    - Transportation planning, 1974 (Box-folder 378: 2)
    - DOT (Department of Transportation), 1972 (Box-folder 378: 3)
    - DOT legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 378: 4)
    - Southern Crossing, bridge information, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 378: 5)
    - Southern Crossing, Ronald Reagan original, 1971 (Box-folder 378: 6)
    - California Highway Commission Report, 1969 (Box-folder 378: 7)
    - Administration transportation initiative documents, 1974 (Box-folder 378: 8)
    - "Southern Crossing: A Brief Report,", 1970 February (Box-folder 378: 9)
    - "Southern Crossing: A Brief Report,", 1971 February (Box-folder 378: 10)
    - "The Critically Injured Patient" published by the Illinois Department of Public Health, 1971 (Box-folder 378: 11)
  - Health and Welfare Agency
    - Documents, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 379: 1)
    - Human resources, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 379: 2)
    - Miscellany, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 379: 3-6)
  - Department of Human Resources development report, 1968 November (Box-folder 379: 7)
  - Human Resources Agency conference materials, 1969 June 5 (Box-folder 379: 8)
  - Guide to the Human Relations Agency, 1970 September (Box-folder 379: 9)
  - Health and Welfare Agency Program, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 380: 1)
  - California Commission on Aging, annual report, 1971 (Box-folder 380: 2)
  - Child care programs, 1973 (Box-folder 380: 3)
  - Task Force on Management of Department of Rehabilitation, 1972 (Box-folder 380: 4)
  - Legislation, Health and Welfare Agency, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 380: 5-11)
  - Health, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 381: 1-7)
  - Task Force on California Organization for Health Services, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 381: 8)
  - Catastrophic health insurance legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 381: 9)
  - "National Health Insurance," Los Angeles Times, 1974 June 14 (Box-folder 382: 1)
  - Illinois health care information, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 382: 2)
  - Los Angeles County Medical Association, 1973 (Box-folder 382: 3)
  - Health care system publications, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 382: 4)
  - Assembly concurrent Resolution No. 80, relative to foreign medical graduates, 1972 (Box-folder 382: 5)
  - Medi-Cal
    - Clippings and memoranda, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 382: 6)
    - Management system information, 1974 (Box-folder 382: 7)
    - General, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 382: 8)
    - Clippings and memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 383: 1)
    - Miscellany, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 383: 2-7)
    - Program, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 383: 8)
    - Litigation, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 384: 1)
    - Task Force on Implementation of Proposed Medi-Cal Management Systems, 1969 (Box-folder 384: 2)
  - "A Guide to Screening for Early and Periodic Screening, Diagnosis, and Treatment Program (EPSDT)," Medicaid, 1974 June (Box-folder 384: 3)
  - Mental health information, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 384: 4-8)
  - Mental health information (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 385: 1-2)
  - Department of Mental Hygiene, 1969, 1972 (Box-folder 385: 3)
  - Mental health, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 385: 4)
  - Edited transcript of hearing of the Subcommittee on Mental Health, 1964 (Box-folder 385: 5)
  - Mental health report by Larry Sosowsky, 1974 June (Box-folder 385: 6)
  - Alcoholism, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 385: 7)
  - Advisory Committee on Alcoholism, Governor's Coordinating Council on Alcohol Problems, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 385: 8)
  - Drug abuse, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 386: 1-7)
  - Drug abuse (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 387: 1-2)
  - Narcotics and Dangerous Drug Abuse Council Meeting, 1968 October 24 (Box-folder 387: 3)
  - Narcotics, Synanon, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 387: 4)
  - Narcotics, drug use by juveniles, 1967 (Box-folder 387: 5)
  - Narcotics, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 387: 6)
  - Narcotic and drug abuse programs, 1968 (Box-folder 387: 7)
  - Narcotic and drug control programs, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 387: 8)
  - Narcotics and dangerous drugs, 1969 (Box-folder 387: 9)
  - California veterans and drug abuse report, 1972 (Box-folder 387: 10)
  - Border Narcotics Task Force, 1969 (Box-folder 387: 11)
  - Drug abuse legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 387: 12)
  - "The California Plan for Drug Abuse Prevention,", 1973 (Box-folder 388: 1)
  - Annual report of the Narcotics Rehabilitation Advisory Council, 1968 (Box-folder 388: 2)
  - Department of Human Resources Development, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 388: 3-4)
  - Employment, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 388: 5-10)
  - Employment (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 389: 1-4)
  - California Labor Market bulletin, 1973 (Box-folder 389: 5)
  - Minimum wage, federal, 1974 (Box-folder 389: 6)
  - Unemployment situation, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 389: 7)
  - Together Project, 1972 (Box-folder 389: 8)
  - Business, industry, and labor, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 389: 9)
  - Employment, youth, 1968 (Box-folder 389: 10)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1974 (Box-folder 389: 11)
  - Federal Fair Labor Standards Act, 1974 (Box-folder 389: 12)
  - Federal Employment Security Automated Reporting System (ESARS) Program, 1970 (Box-folder 389: 13)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1974 (Box-folder 389: 14)
  - Manpower Policy Task Force, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 389: 15-16)
  - California experience with the Federal Emergency Employment Act of 1971, 1973 June (Box-folder 389: 17)
  - Presentation to the Cabinet on manpower programs, 1971 (Box-folder 390: 1)
  - Manpower report of the President, 1972 (Box-folder 390: 2)
  - California Job Training and Placement Council, final report, 1968 (Box-folder 390: 3)
  - Department of Corrections
    - General, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 390: 4)
    - Corrections, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 391: 1-5)
    - Adult Authority Manual of Statistics, 1966 (Box-folder 391: 6)
    - Corrections, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 392: 1-3)
    - Department of Corrections, 1969 (Box-folder 392: 4)
    - Corrections Agency director memoranda, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 392: 5)
    - Youth and Adult Corrections Agency, R. A. McGee, 1967 (Box-folder 392: 6)
    - Corrections, prisoner, parolee population management, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 392: 7)
    - Duty officers' reports, prisons, 1973 (Box-folder 392: 8)
    - State prison situation, 1971 (Box-folder 392: 9)
    - Correspondence from Hawaii regarding Amulu newspaper column from Folsom, 1968 (Box-folder 392: 10)
    - Prison incidents, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 392: 11)
    - Women's Board of Terms and Parole, 1973 (Box-folder 392: 12)
    - Adult authority, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 392: 13)
    - Prison planning, 1973 (Box-folder 392: 14)
    - Correctional policy and procedures, 1970 (Box-folder 392: 15)
    - Correctional services study, 1970 (Box-folder 392: 16)
    - Corrections legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 392: 17)
    - Department of Youth Authority, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 393: 1)
    - Task Force on Crime in California Prisons, 1970, 1974 (Box-folder 393: 2)
    - Task Force on Probation and Parole, 1972 (Box-folder 393: 3)
    - Probation subsidy reports, 1972 (Box-folder 393: 4-5)
    - Prison reform reports, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 393: 6-7)
    - "Juvenile Delinquency: The Core Problem" report, 1970 July (Box-folder 394: 1)
    - Interim report of the Ohio Citizens' Task Force on Corrections, 1971 (Box-folder 394: 2)
    - "Institutions" report, 1971 July (Box-folder 394: 3)
    - "Field Services" report, 1971 July (Box-folder 394: 4)
    - "The System" report, 1971 July (Box-folder 394: 5)
    - "Report to Governor Ronald Reagan on Violence in California Prisons,", 1971 October 7 (Box-folder 395: 1)
    - California laws relating to youthful offenders, 1968 January (Box-folder 395: 2)
    - Assembly Criminal Procedure Committee, 1967 November 14 (Box-folder 395: 3)
    - "The Organization of State Correctional Services in the Control and Treatment of Crime and Delinquency" report, 1967 April 21 (Box-folder 395: 4)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO)
    - General, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 395: 5-7)
    - General (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 396: 1-6)
    - General (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 397: 1-3)
    - Programs, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 397: 4-5)
    - General, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 397: 6-8)
    - Programs in California, 1972 (Box-folder 397: 9)
    - California review of OEO programs, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 397: 10)
    - Programs, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 397: 11)
    - Federal, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 397: 12)
    - Greater L.A. Community Action Agency, 1974 (Box-folder 397: 13)
    - Programs policy and planning, 1972 (Box-folder 397: 14)
    - Oakland Economic Development Council, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 398: 1-2)
    - Oakland OEO program, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 398: 3)
    - Southern Alameda County Economic Opportunity Agency, 1973 (Box-folder 398: 4)
    - Jacaban, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 398: 5)
    - La Posada Camp, 1972 (Box-folder 398: 6)
    - Community Alert Patrol, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 398: 7)
    - Community Services Act, 1974 (Box-folder 398: 8)
    - Housing Assistance Council, 1972 (Box-folder 398: 9)
    - Grant action approval, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 398: 10-11)
    - Data on programs approved and vetoed, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 399: 1)
    - Vetoes, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 399: 2-4)
    - State Economic Opportunity Office (SEOO) assistance grant, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 399: 5)
    - Demonstration grant, State Economic Opportunity Office (SEOO), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 399: 6)
    - Annual report, California State Office of Minority Business Enterprise, 1973 August 30 (Box-folder 399: 7)
    - "A Proposal for the Establishment of an Affiliate of the Office of Minority Business Enterprise,", 1972 April (Box-folder 399: 8)
    - "Opportunity Funding Corporation: The 1st Report", 1972 June (Box-folder 399: 9)
    - Status report and memoranda for the State Office of Economic Opportunity, 1972 (Box-folder 399: 10)
    - Narcotic Prevention and Rehabilitation Project, Economic and Youth Opportunities Agency, 1970 June 1 (Box-folder 399: 11)
    - Management audit report and memoranda of the Economic and Youth Opportunities Agency, 1972 June (Box-folder 399: 12)
    - State Office of Economic Opportunity, State Technical Assistance Refunding for 1972 (Box-folder 400: 1)
    - State Economic Opportunity Office (SEOO) reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 400: 2)
    - Review of the management and operations of the California Economic Opportunity Office, 1973 (Box-folder 400: 3)
    - Legal services, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 400: 4-5)
    - Legal services programs, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 400: 6)
    - Legal assistance plans, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 400: 7)
    - Memoranda, 1971 (Box-folder 400: 8)
    - Hearing on the funding of CRLA and the Experimental Legal Services Project, 1971 (Box-folder 400: 9)
    - Legal assistance plans, administration, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 401: 1-2)
    - Legal assistance plans, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 401: 3)
    - Legal services programs, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 401: 4)
    - Legal services corporation, 1974 (Box-folder 401: 5)
    - Legal services foundation, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 401: 6)
    - Federal legal services proposals, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 401: 7)
    - Legal service programs, 1972 (Box-folder 402: 1)
    - Legal services experimental project, 1972 (Box-folder 402: 2-4)
    - Advisory Committee to the California State OEO on the Legal Services Experiment report, 1972 (Box-folder 402: 5)
    - Planning report and proposals for the California Legal Services Experiment, 1972 (Box-folder 402: 6)
    - California Rural Legal Assistance (CRLA)
      - General, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 403: 1-5)
      - General (cont'd.), 1967-1973 (Box-folder 404: 1-2)
      - CRLA investigation, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 404: 3)
      - Memoranda, notes, correspondence, 1964, 1971 (Box-folder 404: 4)
      - CRLA investigation clippings, 1971 (Box-folder 404: 5)
      - General, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 404: 6)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) legal programs, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 405: 1)
      - General, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box-folder 405: 2-3)
      - Clippings, 1970-197 (Box-folder 405: 4)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box-folder 406: 1-6)
      - Clippings (cont'd.), 1971 (Box-folder 407: 1-5)
    - State Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) to Federal Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Evaluation Volume I-II, 1971 April 29 (Box-folder 408: 1-5)
  - Welfare
    - Welfare information, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 409: 1)
    - Fresno Service Center Focus, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 409: 2)
    - Welfare information, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 409: 3-7)
    - Welfare information, 1970 (Box-folder 410: 1)
    - "Reform," K. W. Lee series in the Sacramento Union, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 410: 2)
    - Welfare information, 1970 (Box-folder 410: 3-4)
    - Reform, 1970 (Box-folder 410: 5)
    - Ronald Reagan original, 1970 (Box-folder 410: 6)
    - State Department of Social Welfare public hearings, 1970 (Box-folder 410: 7)
    - Welfare information, 1971 (Box-folder 411: 1-6)
    - Welfare information (cont'd.), 1971 (Box-folder 412: 1)
    - Reform, 1971 (Box-folder 412: 2)
    - Governor's Task Force on Public Assistance, 1970 (Box-folder 412: 3)
    - Medi-Cal reform implementation, 1971 (Box-folder 412: 4)
    - Medical reform, 1971 (Box-folder 412: 5-7)
    - Reform evaluation and results, 1972 (Box-folder 413: 1)
    - Reform, Beilenson complaints, 1972 (Box-folder 413: 2)
    - Human Relations Agency, welfare reform, 1971 (Box-folder 413: 3)
    - Reform program, public support, 1971 (Box-folder 413: 4-5)
    - Welfare information, 1972 (Box-folder 413: 6-8)
    - "Aid to Families with Dependent Children" and "Aid to Students 18-21 Years of Age,", 1972 (Box-folder 413: 9)
    - Reform legislation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 413: 10)
    - Welfare information, 1973 (Box-folder 413: 11)
    - Social Welfare Management Study Task Force, 1972 (Box-folder 413: 12)
    - Department of Social Welfare, 1973 (Box-folder 413: 13)
    - Reform, 1974 (Box-folder 413: 14)
    - Welfare information, 1974 (Box-folder 413: 15)
    - Abortion information, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 414: 1)
    - "Public Welfare in California," report by Department of Social Welfare, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 414: 2)
    - "Unplanned Parenthood" study, 1974 (Box-folder 414: 3)
    - "Childcare: A Challenge for Industry" report, 1971 (Box-folder 414: 4)
    - "Our California Welfare Mess," report for Senate Republican Caucus, 1970 (Box-folder 414: 5)
    - "The Recipient Fraud Incidence Study,", 1970 (Box-folder 414: 6)
    - "State Social Welfare Board: A Perspective on the Child Support Provisions of the Welfare Reform Act of 1971" (Box-folder 414: 7)
    - "Preliminary Report of the Task Force on Absent Parent Child Support,", 1970 (Box-folder 414: 8)
    - "California Welfare: A Legislative Program for Reform,", 1969 (Box-folder 414: 9)
    - Welfare information report, 1971 (Box-folder 414: 10)
    - Possible federal actions to reduce costs of welfare, 1970 (Box-folder 415: 1)
    - Conformity issues, 1970 (Box-folder 415: 2)
    - State Department of Social Welfare Federal Compliance, 1970 (Box-folder 415: 3)
    - "Public Welfare: Time for Change," final report, 1970 (Box-folder 415: 4)
    - "A Plan for a 'Systems' Approach and Reorganization of Social Services in California for the Reagan Administration,", 1967 (Box-folder 415: 5)
    - Governor's welfare program study, 1971 (Box-folder 415: 6)
    - Management study, Alameda County Welfare Department, 1971 (Box-folder 415: 7)
    - Senate Committee on Health and Welfare, 1971 November (Box-folder 415: 8-10)
    - "Meeting the Challenge: A Responsible Program for Welfare and Medi-Cal Reform,", 1971 (Box-folder 415: 11)
    - "Guide for Administration and Conduct of a Coordinated Child Support Program by California Counties,", 1971 (Box-folder 416: 1)
    - "California's Blueprint for National Welfare Reform, Proposals for Improving the Food Stamp and AFDC Programs,", 1974 (Box-folder 416: 2)
    - State Social Welfare Board position statement, "Aliens in California,", 1973 (Box-folder 416: 3)
    - Welfare documents, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 416: 4-5)
    - Martin v. California v. California Welfare Rights Organization Inc., 1971 (Box-folder 416: 6)
    - "Welfare Reform in California Moving to Complete the Task- Preliminary Report,", 1974 (Box-folder 416: 7)
    - Welfare federal, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 416: 8-10)
    - Federal Welfare Reform Plan, 1970 (Box-folder 417: 1)
    - HR-1, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 417: 2)
    - Federal, 1971 (Box-folder 417: 3-5)
    - Federal, material Prepared for Ronald Reagan prior to San Clemente meeting, 1971 (Box-folder 417: 6)
    - Federal, 1972 (Box-folder 417: 7-8)
    - Welfare withheld, 1972 (Box-folder 417: 9)
    - Material sent to Senate Finance Committee, testimony transcript, 1972 (Box-folder 418: 1)
    - Ronald Reagan presentation on welfare reform before U.S. Senate Finance Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 418: 2)
    - Ronald Reagan presentation on welfare reform before Senate Finance Committee and memorandum from Senator Russell Long, 1972 (Box-folder 418: 3)
    - Ronald Reagan presentation on welfare reform before Senate Finance Committee, speech cards and annotated speech copy, 1972 (Box-folder 418: 4)
    - Senate Finance Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 418: 5)
    - Federal welfare, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 418: 6-7)
    - Federal welfare, original Weinberger note to Edwin Meese, 1974 (Box-folder 418: 8)
    - Federal welfare, conformity, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 418: 9-10)
    - Federal welfare, undated (Box-folder 418: 11)
    - HR1-SSI, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 418: 12-13)
  - Senate Act H.R. 3153, 1973 November 30 (Box-folder 419: 1)